[YUTA]
With supplies being limited,
we'll need to add a rule
allowing passage
in and out of the colony.
But I can't afford
to let players like Dhruv,
who attack people
indiscriminately,
leave the barriers.
I should wait until the players
like him are eliminated
from the other colonies first.
Communication between colonies
is a must.
There's the two rules
Fushiguro proposed.
A means of communication,
and passage
in and out of the colonies.
So we'll need
four additional rules
to get the situation
under control.
Everyone's still at their
physical and emotional limit
from Shibuya.
Gojo.
I won't let you kill
your best friend twice.
I'll kill Kenjaku myself.
I'll get the 400 points
on my own.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Okay, you can all come out now.
I think we should continue
making our way north
to the edge of the barrier.
[GIRL] Can you carry me?
[MOTHER]
Just hang in there, sweetheart.
Why don't we take a quick rest?
We're safe here.
This stadium
was being controlled
by the sorcerer I just defeated.
Any player that comes along
will be pretty hesitant to--
-[rumbling]
-[MAN 1] What's that sound?
[YUTA] Quick.
Get into the stadium.
[MAN 2] Let's go!
-[panicked chatter]
-Hurry up.
[men panting, whimpering]
[man in blue hoodie screams]
[gasps]
Help! Help me!
[grunts]
[♪ intense music playing]
[YUTA] Wait,
are these cockroaches real?
[vomits]
[YUTA] Damn!
-Rika, knock it down!
-[MAN 1] Hurry!
-[RIKA] Okay!
-[girl whimpers]
[MAN 1] Run!
♪
-Kogane, is that a player?
-Yes.
That is a player
called Kurourushi.
[YUTA] So some players
are cursed spirits.
EPISODE 59
SENDAI COLONY
FESTERING LIFE SWORD
[whooshing]
[slashes]
[clangs, thuds]
[grunts]
[YUTA] I'm being watched.
Likely, it's the other
two players with high points.
[KUROURUSHI]
Why do you interfere?
[YUTA]
Kurourushi is a cursed spirit.
[KUROURUSHI] Why do you kill us?
[YUTA] I can exorcise it.
I just have to drive
positive energy
from my reverse cursed technique
into its body.
I can ask you the same question.
But...
[KUROURUSHI] Because
I like the taste of iron!
[YUTA] I don't want
those other two players
to know I can use
reverse cursed technique.
Rika's protecting everyone
in the stadium.
So I have to
exorcise Kurourushi
without using Rika
or my reverse cursed technique.
[clangs]
[KUROURUSHI] Blinding.
Blinding.
[slashes]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[sword clanging]
[Kurourushi growls]
[slashes]
[coughs]
-[mini Kuros squealing]
-[Yuta groans]
[groans]
[breathing laboriously]
[grunts]
[struggling breaths]
[Kurourushi growls]
[Yuta grunts]
-[bites]
-[Kurourushi gasps]
[wind whooshing]
[cracking]
[KOGANE] You have gained
five points for a kill.
[TAKAKO] I see
that you can use...
-...reverse cursed technique.
-[gasps]
[Yuta grunts]
[YUTA] What was that?
-A strike?
-[Takako grunts]
[grunts]
[glass shatters]
[YUTA] My arm is back to normal.
I feel fine.
Her technique probably
manipulates space.
But I guess
she can't use that space
to crush her opponents.
It seems to create distortions
like a funhouse mirror.
[TAKAKO] You're wondering
about my technique?
It treats the sky as a surface.
Here, let me show you.
[YUTA]
She's revealing her technique.
[TAKAKO]
Hurry up and attack already.
[YUTA] I have to ask.
You're not someone
who's gonna complain
about getting killed, are you?
I mean, I can understand
powerless people
getting desperate for points,
but a strong person like you
can claim points
whenever they want.
So what's your reason
for actively seeking a fight?
[TAKAKO] This little brat.
Seriously?
Are you modern-day sorcerers
that casual about incarnation?
To us from the old school,
this means coming back
from the dead.
People who lived out
their lives without regrets
wouldn't accept
Kenjaku's offer, would they?
He's really pissing me off.
I like to think
of the Culling Game
as the first step toward
a chance at a second life.
Keep in mind that Kenjaku
set the stage for this.
Anything could happen.
We need to earn points
to prepare ourselves.
I wonder if someone like you
has any friends or lovers.
Huh?
You know what?
Until recently, I didn't
have any friends either.
Not that I feel sorry for you.
[TAKAKO] Hmm, this feeling.
It's like he's hunting
for things that trigger me.
[YUTA] Your pain was caused
thousands of years ago.
The people alive today have
nothing to do with your regrets.
How many have to die
until you finally feel avenged?
Wait just a minute.
Are you one of the Fujiwara?
How can anyone
from your bloodline
understand me?
[Yuta grunts]
[Takako grunting]
[Takako growling]
[RYU] Granite Blast.
[YUTA] Ishigori?
[TAKAKO]
It came from that rooftop.
Too close for comfort.
[YUTA] Even with Rika
protecting the stadium,
a direct hit from an attack
on that level
will leave several people dead.
So I have to take
Ishigori out first.
[TAKAKO] Now that Kurourushi
and Dhruv are gone,
I have no reason
to let Ishigori run free.
I'll take both him
and Okkotsu...
-[YUTA] Now.
-[TAKAKO]...out.
[RYU] Granite Blast!
Come on.
Don't disappoint me.
He's gone?
No. That's where Okkotsu
dug a hole earlier.
Can't you fight
without blowing up
everything around you?
Oh, but that won't satisfy
my hunger, Okkotsu.
JUJUTSU KAISEN
Would you tell a starving kid
with a feast in front of him
to take his time and eat slower?
[YUTA] Wouldn't anyone?
[RYU] I guess so.
Most probably would.
That was a bad example.
My first run at life wasn't
completely lacking flavor.
Some of the guys I fought
had real backbone.
I even met a nice woman, too.
Frankly, it'd be hard to say
I had any regrets at all.
This vague hunger
I constantly feel
is always gnawing
at me, Okkotsu.
Everyone's always wondering
what I'm so unsatisfied about.
These cigarettes have
a slightly sweet aftertaste.
You know what it was?
There was no dessert in my life.
[YUTA] Here it comes.
[thuds]
[laughs]
[punching]
[RYU] Why am I unsatisfied?
I think you know!
-[gasps]
-[chuckles]
[groans]
[RYU] I'm unsatisfied
because I'm not fulfilled!
[grunts]
[Ryu grunts]
[gasps]
You'd better not be crushed.
[grunts]
[choking]
[grunting]
[grunts]
[RYU] Hey, watch the hair.
[YUTA] Nice.
[Ryu grunts]
Not calling your shikigami?
I can't right now.
Not with you going wild.
[RYU] Oh, that's a shame.
[running]
[YUTA] He's probably
trying to limit where I can go.
But I'll break through...
head - on!
Sweet!
That's it, Okkotsu!
Keep on coming!
[YUTA] His cursed energy,
so precise!
-Here's your reward!
-[gasps]
Uh-oh.
I overheated my hair.
[creaks]
[crashes]
[grunts]
[RYU] You're good, Okkotsu.
Could you be the one?
Are you my dessert?
[Yuta grunts]
You're great!
Best I've seen so far!
[TAKAKO]
What I strike isn't the person,
but the surface of the sky.
[shatters]
Thin Ice Breaker!
Get lost, you pile of vomit!
Shut your mouth,
-dick cheese!
-[gasps]
[chuckles]
This guy's resilient.
Glad you're alive.
I wanted to torment you
some more.
[groans] What a hit.
That was the first time
I've been forced
to eat my own technique.
Reverse cursed technique
is a pain to deal with,
but it burns cursed energy
like crazy.
We're finally seeing the bottom
of your reserves, Okkotsu.
No matter how high - end
the sweet shop is,
seeing the displays empty
at closing time
is always disappointing.
Guess it wasn't you.
[panting]
[YUTA] I wanted
to gain more distance
from everyone in the stadium,
keep them out of harm's way.
Oh, well.
Come to me, Rika.
Give me everything!
[both gasp]
[TAKAKO] His shikigami
completely manifested?
[RYU] How does that work?
And he's swelling
with cursed energy again!
[RIKA]
Which would you like, Yuta?
Thank you.
I'll take that one.
[chuckles]
[NARRATOR] Rika is
the stockpile of cursed energy
and the externalization
of Okkotsu's technique.
It remained with him
after Rika Orimoto passed on.
While connected to Rika
through the ring,
he gains the following.
Use of his cursed technique,
the complete manifestation
of Rika,
and the cursed energy
supplied by Rika.
Yuta can remain
connected to Rika
for five minutes.
[YUTA] Okay.
Let's go.
[TAKAKO] Don't
underestimate me. [gasps]
[Yuta hisses]
[YUTA] Don't move.
[TAKAKO] Snake eyes and fangs.
I can't move.
[punching]
[Takako groaning]
Oh, man.
You are super sweet, huh?
[Takako groaning]
[YUTA] Rika.
-[RIKA] Right!
-[RYU] Yeah!
[RYU] Oh, no!
[thuds]
[strains]
That was close! Huh?
[grunts] You can't
get rid of me that easy!
♪
[Takako grunts]
-[Ryu groans]
-[gasps]
[Yuta groans]
[Rika gasps]
[hisses]
[RIKA] You!
You hurt Yuta!
[Takako gasps]
[grunts]
[gasps]
[whooshing]
[YUTA] What now?
[RYU] Let's go!
[Yuta grunts]
[laughs]
[YUTA] Even with this,
I can't fully block it.
-Wanna go?
-[grunts]
[Rika grunts]
[gasps]
[Takako grunts]
[growls]
[cracks]
[gasps]
[TAKAKO] Thin Ice Breaker!
[scoffs]
The Sun, Moon, and Stars Squad
was Fujiwara Clan's assassins.
We lived in darkness and served
with selfless devotion.
We were even forbidden
from having our own names.
Yet that man
once granted me a name.
So he could execute me instead
for his crime
of slaying his own kin.
[scoffs] Fujiwara!
[RYU] I've still got
a strong appetite!
[growls]
Let's keep chowing down!
[TAKAKO]
It's always you, Fujiwara!
You're always getting in my way!
Are you that afraid of me?
Afraid of me
becoming my own person?
-[hisses]
-[grunts]
[NARRATOR] Okkotsu
defeated Dhruv Lakdawalla,
whose technique made
the path of his shikigami
into his domain,
which cut into anything
it touched.
[slashes]
[gasps]
[TAKAKO]
This is Dhruv's technique.
Does that mean
Okkotsu's technique is Copy?
[Yuta grunting]
[Takako grunting]
[Ryu grunting]
[punching]
[YUTA] I don't know
what my ancestors did to you,
but that has nothing
to do with me.
If you live only
for your own sake,
you're eventually
going to reach your limit.
[TAKAKO] Shut up!
Live for the sake of others?
You think I'll eventually
reach my limit?
Stop barking those things at me!
It's easy for you to say.
You've already become someone!
[snickers]
[grunts]
[♪ tense music playing]
[RYU] Quit your whining!
Because at this point,
words are meaningless!
[ALL] Domain Expansion!
Yuta! Give him back!
[TAKAKO] Even if it tries
to penetrate the barrier later.
[RYU]
I ain't gonna drag this out!
Let's settle this,
nice and sweet!
[NARRATOR] At that moment,
the black devil
of the modern age...
[KUROURUSHI] I told you,
I like the taste of iron!
[NARRATOR]
...flew into the barriers.
[all gasp]
[NARRATOR] Kurourushi
had completed parthenogenesis
before going dormant.
So Kurourushi
was still alive and well
as a cursed spirit.
The complex forces
of their domains
had been keeping
the three sorcerers in check.
But this intruder
was unexpected.
And so the barriers...
collapsed.
[TAKAKO]
How's Kurourushi still alive?
-[Yuta grunts]
-[Takako gasps]
-[grunts]
-[shatters]
[TAKAKO] Damn!
I can't use my technique
right after Domain Expansion.
-[Kurourushi growls]
-[Takako gasps]
[Rika chomping]
How dare you take my arm!
-Fujiwara!
-[RYU] Enough, Uro.
Quiet.
You and the roach were
never invited to my table.
Granite Blast.
[explosion]
[NARRATOR] Ishigori's technique
is Cursed Energy Discharge.
It's an extremely simple attack,
but it performs just as well,
even when his technique
is burnt out.
[Kurourushi growling]
Now.
Welcome to my table...
Okkotsu.
-Rika, let's go.
-[growls]
[NARRATOR] Okkotsu can discharge
a high volume of cursed energy,
but only while Rika
is completely manifested.
However, his maximum output
is slightly inferior
to Ishigori's.
So he planned to charge
and unleash his cursed energy
before Ishigori
reached maximum output.
- [Yuta gasps]
- But he changed his mind.
LET'S LET IT ALL OUT!
400 years of longing.
The intense gaze
full of that hunger
melted Yuta Okkotsu's heart,
even though he would
likely never find meaning
in fighting.
All right, just this once.
♪
[both grunt]
[♪ theme song playing]
That was some
seriously sweet stuff, Okkotsu!
[Yuta grunts]
Yeah, attaboy!
Let's keep
this dinner party going!
That big thing
can fire on its own?
But...
its force is weak!
After Domain Expansion
and a meal with me,
even you haven't had
enough time to digest
and recover your full strength.
I'll end this!
Granite Blast!
♪
[NARRATOR]
But Okkotsu's technique...
had already recovered.
[Ryu gasps]
[RYU]
He's using Uro's technique!
I knew he was more than just
a cursed speech user.
And I figured that big thing
probably had
a different technique
from Okkotsu's, too.
So that's it!
Okkotsu's technique is Copy!
But there should be
strenuous conditions on it.
When did he satisfy
those conditions?
While I wasn't looking?
Maybe there aren't any!
[Yuta grunts]
[RYU] That was when he did it!
[YUTA] Thin Ice Breaker!
[Ryu groans]
-[Rika growls]
-[Yuta grunts]
[beeps]
[NARRATOR] Five minutes.
Okkotsu's connection
to Rika was severed.
-[growls]
-[Yuta gasps]
[RIKA] Yuta!
[Yuta grunts]
[RYU] Is this the feeling?
[Yuta groans]
[grunts]
[RYU] There's still more
after going all out!
♪
This is what it's like
to eat dessert!
[chuckles, grunts]
[grunts]
[YUTA] We're done.
[RYU] What?
What does he mean?
[gasps]
♪
[panting]
Was that my technique?
I see.
He sent it sailing back to me
using Uro's technique.
Thank you, Okkotsu.
[cutlery clinks]
I'm full now.
[chuckles]
[thuds]
[gasps]
[sighs]
Okkotsu, you're too soft.
That's not a compliment.
Sparing the life of a sorcerer
who fought to kill you--
[YUTA] There's nothing
to gain from killing you.
Uro told me the same thing.
[RYU] You mean
that woman's still alive?
Well, I guess
my blast was weaker
after my Domain Expansion.
Hey, what was it
she kept going on about?
Were you having a lovers' spat?
Yeah, something like that.
Eh, don't let her get to ya.
[YUTA] There's nothing
I can say to that woman
to change her mind.
Anything I do say
will lead to violence.
You see,
it's because I'm blessed.
[Ryu sighs]
Is that how it works?
Because frankly, I don't get it.
[Yuta sighs] Well, regardless,
can I have your points?
Huh?
Now I get it.
So if we didn't
give you our points,
you would have killed us, right?
[Yuta grunts]
I'm not so sure about that.
[chuckles] All I know is
you should be grateful
to my friends.
THROUGH THE TRANSFER
OF RYU AND TAKAKO'S POINTS,
YUTA OKKOTSU
CAME TO POSSESS 190 POINTS.
[♪ melancholic music playing]
[TAKAKO] You're the one
who's going to reach your limit.
I've seen it.
Be it sorcerer or cursed spirit,
all are driven over the edge
by the same thing.
Overwhelming aggression
that blinds them
to everything else.
Like a calamity.
TO BE CONTINUED
[♪ closing theme song playing]